# Jordan Pearson

**Software Developer** 

(253) 224-0219 jsantipearson@gmail.com github.com/JSantiPearson jsantipearson/github.io/landing

I am an Afro-Latino software developer with a passion for making slick mobile and web applications and developing videogames on platforms like PlayStation 4, PC, and mobile. I want to gain more experience by building impactful applications that can make tedious tasks efficient and stylish.

### **EXPERIENCE**

### Paid Intern — Camouflaj Games — Summer 2019

Camouflaj is a videogame studio based in Bellevue that utilizes VR technology to create groundbreaking AAA titles.

- Streamlined Camouflaj's QA bug reporting workflow through a Python script
- Increased Unity C# script bug fixes by nearly 150% in development of "Iron Man VR", a PlayStation 4 Virtual Reality videogame title

### IT Support — Nintendo of America November 2020 - Present

Nintendo of America is a subsidiary of Nintendo Co. Ltd. that provides video game products and services.

- Primarily solve technical issues and bugs with company software for employees
- Other responsibilities include managing user credentials and assisting with hardware issues

## Founder — Strange Frontier — Summer 2020

Strange Frontier is an Android and iOS app that allows the user to create and use player character sheets for Tabletop RPGs.

 Utilized the React Native JavaScript framework and Google's Firebase platform

# Director — Avarice Island — Spring 2020

Avarice Island was my undergraduate senior capstone in Computer Science, a project lead by myself.

- Pitched, directed, and developed an impressive videogame demo utilizing the Unity game engine
- Implemented over 10 enemies with adaptive AI and three full levels with unique boss fights
- Wrote over 50 scripts in C#, created a responsive UI and an intuitive UX

# Front End Developer — TheatreBot Fall 2017 - 2018

TheatreBot is a web application that simplifies the theatre callback process using a scheduling algorithm and intuitive UI

- TheatreBot automatically schedules actor auditions and callbacks for theatrical productions
- Utilized the MEAN stack (Node, Express, Angular, and MongoDB) to create a crisp front end

### **EDUCATION**

# University of Puget Sound, Tacoma — Year of 2020

3.5 Cumulative GPA

**B.S Computer Science** 

September 2016 - June 2020 Minor in Spanish

### SKILLS

### **Languages and Technologies**

Mongo/ Express / Angular / Node Java / C / Python Unity / C#

JavaScript / React.js HTML / CSS

React Native

**Linux Command Line** 

#### **Software Skills**

**Version Control (GIT)** 

Jira

Video Editing (Premiere Pro/Windows)

**Office Suite** 

#### **Soft Skills**

Eye for Detail Self Motivated Fast Learner

### **AWARDS**

Dean's List, Spring 2016 Emergency Food Network Volunteer of the Month: July 2015 Beta Theta Pi - Man of Principle Award Phi Eta Sigma Honor Society

### **FUN FACTS**

Fluent in Spanish
2 Year Captain of Improv Comedy Team
Sketch Comedy Writer/Performer

Shakespearean Actor